So Easy to Kill, So Hard to Love
Switchblade Sisters is a action, crime, drama film directed by Jack Hill.
The leader of an inner city girl gang is challenged when
a new girl moves into the neighborhood.
Lace, played by Robbie Lee.
Maggie, played by Joanne Nail.
Patch, played by Monica Gayle.
Dominic, played by Asher Brauner.
Crabs, played by Chase Newhart.
Muff, played by Marlene Clark.
Switchblade Sisters is a 1975 American exploitation action film
detailing the lives of high school-aged female gang members.
It was directed by Jack Hill and stars Joanne Nail, Robbie Lee and Monica Gayle.
The film is also known as The Jezebels, Maggie's Stiletto
Sisters and The Warriors II: Las Navajeras.
The movie was not a success at the box office, but
garnered a cult following later on.
Most of its current popularity can be attributed to film director Quentin Tarantino, who named the picture
a personal favorite and re-released it in 1996 under his Rolling Thunder Pictures label.
The DVD release features an audio commentary track with Hill and Tarantino.
The film's tagline is "So Easy to Kill, So Hard to Love."
The film explores themes of high school, 1970s, gang war, exploitation, gang.
The tone is emotional.